Dean of Undergraduate Studies; Records ua520
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Dean of Undergraduate Studies Records
1958-1986
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
State University of New York at Albany. University College
ua520
8.37 cubic ft.
This collection contains records from the period in which Robert Morris served as Dean of the University College (1966-1970) and Dean of Undergraduate Studies (1970- roughly 1977).
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted.
Acquisition Information
All items in this collection were transferred to the University Libraries, M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives.
Biographical Sketch
Robert Morris started at the State University of New York at Albany in 1966 as Dean of the University College, which had been established in 1963 to oversee academic affairs for freshmen and sophomores. The University College presided over nearly every aspect of academic life for underclassmen, including academic probation, advisement, attendance, and withdrawal. He was later promoted to Dean of Undergraduate Studies, a position in which he oversaw both lower- and upper-division undergraduate education, from 1970 until approximately 1977. Between these two positions, he oversaw all aspects of the administration of undergraduate education at the University, with a focus on the drafting, creation and implementation of policies for students in the lower division.
Scope and Contents
This collection addresses all aspects of the administration of undergraduate education at the University. It includes undergraduate policy manuals, advisement manuals for professors, documentation on changes in various grading policies, correspondence between Morris and various other administrators at the University, budget materials, annual reports, enrollment data, and planning documentation for the Undergraduate Bulletin. There is also correspondence between employees of the University College and other colleges and universities relating to policy creation. The bulk of the material is dated between 1966 and 1978.
Arrangement of the Collection
Files in this collection have been maintained in their original order upon processing.
Education, Higher--Administration; Administrative records; Correspondence; Annual reports; UAlbany Academic Administration; State University of New York at Albany
- Committee on Academic Standing Meting Minutes, 1963-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Academic Reports, 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Academic Information for Undergraduates Students, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- "Your Academic Program" Brochures, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- University College Advisement Manual, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- "Your Academic Program" Brochures, 1964-1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Academic Information Booklets, 1972-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- University College Advisement Manual- VII: Other Ways to Earn College Credit, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- University College Advisement Manual- VIII: Humanities Davison, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- University College Advisement Manual- IX: Math and Science Davison, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- University College Advisement Manual- X: Social Science Davison - XIII: Other Academic Offerings, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Academic Information Booklet Companions, 1973-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- University College Advisement Manual [Afro- American Studies- Business Administration], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- University College Advisement Manual [ Chemistry - History ], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- University College Advisement Manual [ Linguistics - Science], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- University College Advisement Manual [ Social Studies- Traffic Safety], 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- University College Advisement Manual [ 1 of 4 ], 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- University College Advisement Manual [ 1 of 4 ], 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- University College Advisement Manual [ 1 of 4 ], 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- University College Advisement Manual [ 1 of 4 ], 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Undergraduate Manuals, 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Morris Rolex Office of Under Graduate Studies, 1968-1975 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Attitude Survey- University College, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Student Attitude Survey, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Appeals- Undergraduate Admissions, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Admissions- Freshman Delayed, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Admissions Office Info Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Admissions Quota, Undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Advisement, Mathias/ Students, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Advanced Placement, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Administrative Workshop (RBM 1966) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Academic Policy (Working Papers) Office Copy, 1970 September 1 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Academic Policy (Working Papers) Office Copy, 1969 October 30 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Academic Policy (Working Papers) Office Copy, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Academic Affairs Administrators N.E. Reg. Assn, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Academic Action, 1966-1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Academic Dean. Office, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- University Procedures Manual [ 1 of 3 ], 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- University Procedures Manual [ 2 of 3 ], 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- University Procedures Manual [ 3 of 3 ], 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Organization Chart + NTP Performance Program, 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Fulbright Program Correspondence and Notes, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Admissions Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Courses - Approved S/U ( Master File), 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Confidential Bower, Warren, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Confidential VanValkenburgh, M.D. III, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Confidential Wagner, G., 1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Luke Scholars 7-03, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- University College, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Affirmative Action, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Registration, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Honors Graduation, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Scheduling, 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Computing Center, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Office of the Registrar, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- General Studies, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Undergraduate Studies, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Admissions- Transfer, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Office of Undergrad Studies Office of Dean, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Undergraduate Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Undergraduate Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Undergrad Bulletin (Final Copy) ( Under Graduate Academic Regulations), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- UAC Academic Standing Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- UAC Admissions Comm., 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- UAC Curriculum Comm., 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- UAC H & IS Committee, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Pre- UAC Meeting (Monthly), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- UAC Pre UAC Meeting, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- University College Correspondence (Info), 1971 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Undergraduate Studies- Annual Report, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Veterans' Training, 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Visiting Student Program ( Inventory List, Genera Information), 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Withdrawal- Procedures/ Misc., 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Workload Ratios, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- WICHE Modeling System, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- W- Grade Study, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- B.A./ B.S. Distinction, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Computing Center, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Athlete- Academic Achievement of a Proposal, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Advisement " Professional Academic Counseling", 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Advisement, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Advisement, Accad/ UC Associate, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Undergraduate Affairs Committee, 1969 December-1970 December (Box 3, Folder 22)
- College Proficiency Examinations, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Code of Ethics, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Code Book, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Closed Courses- Statement of Central Council, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Census of Majors, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Buffalo, University of, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Computer & University College, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Courses, Miscellaneous Information, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Courses- Review of Scheduling, 1969-1971 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Daily Copies, 1969 September-1970 January (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Daily Copies, 1969 March-August (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Domestic Student Exchange Program Miscellaneous, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Deans' Meetings, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Departmental Programs Majors & The University College, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Disciplines, Information on the, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Domestic Student Exchange Program Illinois, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Domestic Student Exchange Program Montana, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 39)
- Educational Policy Committee, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- E.O.P., 1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- SUNY Faculty- Senate Miscellaneous Materials, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Environmental Studies Second Field Advisory Statement, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Enrollment, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- End of Semester Procedures, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Farmingdale Review Committee, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Financial Aids, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Four Week Grades, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Freshman Matters For Future Study, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Freshman Profiles, 1963-1986 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- General Studies, College of, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- "Getting Through College" Clinic, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Grades, Appeal of Correspondence, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Grades, Appeal of, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Grades, Distribution of, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 55)
- Grading, S/U General, 1967; 1968; 1969 (Box 3, Folder 56)
- Grading S/U Policy, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 57)
- Independent Study/ Community Service, 1966 January-1970 December (Box 3, Folder 58)
- Independent Study- Michigan State U., 1969 (Box 3, Folder 59)
- Instruction Resources Center, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 60)
- Kettering Project- on College Teaching, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 61)
- Language Requirement, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 62)
- Language- Summer Institute, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 63)
- Library Science, Scholl of, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 64)
- Master Plan - Correspondence/ Misc., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 65)
- Middle State Association, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 66)
- National Association of Student Personnel Administration Journal NASPA, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 67)
- New Patterns of Undergraduate Educational- Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 68)
- Organization Chart + NTP Performance Program, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 69)
- Organization Charts, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 70)
- Physical Education- Waivers, etc., 1961-1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Overseas Academic Program, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Readmissions Policy, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Registrar's Office, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Reorganization, 1958-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Second Fields, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Selective Service Information, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy Manual, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Student Records Memoranda, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- New York State Regents Fellows For Graduate Students, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- New York City Urban Fellowship, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Wheelock Scholarship- Men, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Wheelock Scholarship- Men, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Ben V. Smith Scholarship Fund-- Alumni Association, 1963-1986 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Sales Peirce Joint Scholarship, 1963-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Macilwaine, Shields Prize Fund, 1963-1986 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Jenkins Memorial Scholarship, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Arrive Elddred Scholarship Delta Kappa Gamma Awards, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Awards, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Business & Professional Women's Club of Albany, L, Shufelt Award, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- DAR, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Scholarships, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Academic Action, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Academic Planning For, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Academic Policy Working Papers, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Administrative Salary Plan, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Admissions Office, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Admissions- New Process, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Budget Proposal Procedures, 1973-1973 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Pre-registration, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Presidents Office, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Professional Service Tittles, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Public- University Relations, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Registration- Cancellation, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Registrar, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Register Staff, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Residence- Legal Opinion, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Pace, Campus, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Student Conduct, Behavior, Rights, Freedoms, Etc., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Sub-Committee Admissions and Transfer of the Council of Academic Vice-- Presidents, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Archives, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- SUNY- Seal Project, The, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Teacher Education- Proposed revision of Professional Sequence, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Title Specifications, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Transcripts- Undergraduate Applications to Graduate Study, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Two- Year College Student Envelopment Center, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Two- Year College Study, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- UAC, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- UAC Annual Repost, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Undergraduate Academic Council Annual Report, 1971-1973 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Undergraduate Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Undergraduate Collation, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Academic Policy Manual, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Undergraduate Studies-- Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Undergraduate Studies Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Dr. Morris' Copy of Manual, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- University College ( General), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- University College-- Annual Report, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- University College Annual Report, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- University College, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- University College: Past, Present and Future ? (P. Lieberman ) (4/72), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Staff Roster - University College, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- University System Analysis, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Visiting Student Program, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Vocational Technical Education, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- CEEB, 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Closed Courses- Statement of Central Council, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Code Book, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Courses- Master File of Misc. Correspondence ( Code Book, Computing Center Etc.), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Courses - Miscellaneous Information, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Courses, Review of Scheduling, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Courses - Review of Scheduling, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Crisis, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Cross-Registration Procedures, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Cure RBM, 1970 April 16 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Curriculum Committee, 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Curriculum Committee, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Day Care, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Dean's List, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Degrees, Conferring of, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Degree, Commend Elements of, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Degree Clearance, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Diplomas, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Educational Policies Council, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Evaluation Courses & Teachers, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Evaluation, Office of, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Field Trips- Policy on, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Grievance Procedure for Students, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Info on General Studies, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Leave of Absence Proud, 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Liberal Arts and Science, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Major Fields of Study, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1976 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Awards and Statistical Memoranda, 1969-1972 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Office of Evaluation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Old Westbury, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Organization, 1969-1971 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Orientation, Academic, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Overseas Academic Programs, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Pre-registration, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Physical Education Waivers, etc., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Pre- Processional Advisement Committee, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Physical Education Department (historic), 1954-1971 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Procedures, Office, 1963-1986 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Sorokin, Philip L., 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Task Force on Regionalism Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Summer Planning Conferences, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Ruffed, Paul ( a proposal), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Resident Assistants C.R.A.P, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Regulations: SUNY Coward Of Trustees, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Regulations: Commissioner of Education, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Registrar's Office, Review of, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Budget, 1968-1969 (Box 5, Folder 35)
- General Correspondence Budget, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- "The Professor, The Student and The Learning Relationship" Report, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Academic Policy, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Admissions Advisory ( Chancellor ), 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Admissions-- Appeal Of, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Admissions Correspondence, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Admissions, Freshman (Delayed) A Proposal, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Admissions - Info. Correspondence, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Admissions Office Off- Campus Meeting, 1971 September 23 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Admissions, Open ( A Proposal ), 1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Advancement Placement, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Advisement, Academic/ UC Associate, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Affirmative Action, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Albany Street Academy-- Sister Harmon, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- ASP- Credit for, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Athletic Edibility, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Attendance Procedures, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Biology-- Provost's Advisory Committee, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Business, School of, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Calendars, Academic, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Calendar-- Pre Election Recess, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Calendar, Proposed, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Campus Issues-- Communications Teams, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Campus Issues -- Miscellaneous, 1971 January (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Capes Issues-- Miscellaneous, 1970 May-1970 December (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Capes Issues-- Miscellaneous, 1970 January-1970 April (Box 5, Folder 61)
- CEED Scores, Etc. (LL Report ), 1970 September (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Chancellor's Meetings, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Chancellor's Student Cabinet, 1970 April 24 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Closed Courses- Statement by Central Council, 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Computing Center, 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Registrar's Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Registrar's Correspondence Fall, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Registrar's Correspondence, 1970 May 1 (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Registrar's Correspondence, 1971 January-1971 May (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Registrar's Correspondence, 1971 September (Box 6, Folder 2)
- I-B 2 UC Statistics ( Advancement Analysis, etc., ), 1966 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- I-B 2 UC Dean's List and Probation List UC, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- I-b 2 UC Statistics (Advancement), 1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Staff Roster Academic Program Brochure, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- University Scholars, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- University Office of Evaluation, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- U.C. Trailing Sessions, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- U.C. Staff Meeting, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- University College - Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Transfer Credits, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Transfer Articulations (conference ), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Summer Planning Conference, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Student Faculty Ratios, 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Student Evaluations of Courses and Teachers (SECT), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Speeches, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Social Security Number, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Second Fields, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- General College, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Locker, Marvin J. (SUNYB), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Grade Appeal Process Proposals and Documentation, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Grades, Appeal of Correspondence, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Grievances ( Orlofsky/ Students), 1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Students HOLOS, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Honors and Independent Study, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Independent Study (UNI 300-301), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Independent Study and Community Service ( Evaluation of ), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Independent Study/ Community Service, 1971 January-1971 December (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Innovative Educations, Office of ( M. Orlofsky), 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Independent Study, Michigan State Survey, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Internship Program, Proposed, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Judicial Workshop, 1971 February (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Kettering Project on College Teaching, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Language Credits ( Proposal for Granting ) (B. Gray), 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Major, Change of, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Media, CAI-SUNY Senate, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Middle State Association Report [ 1 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Middle State Association Report [ 2 of 2], 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Moline School, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Ministry, Campus, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Office Correspondence, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- New Patters In Under graduate Education- Miscellaneous, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Computing Center/ Printing of Grades on Transcript, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Computing Center Priorities, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- "Concerns Table", 1971 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Daily Copies, 1971 January-1971 February (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Daily Copies, 1971 September-1971 November (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Daily Copies, 1971 March-1971 April (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Daily Copies, 1971 May-1971 August (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Daily Copies, 1970 November-1970 December (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Daily Copies, 1970 September-1970 October (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Daily Copies, 1970 February-1970 August (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Dismissals, Academic ( Working Papers), 1971 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Double Major, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Draper Complex, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- School Of Education, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Enrollment, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Enrollment Fall, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 59)
- EOP (General ), 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 60)
- E.O.P., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 61)
- E.O.P., 1971 January-1971 December (Box 6, Folder 62)
- Equal Opportunity, 1965-1971 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- ETS, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Evaluation of Faculty(Jap. Grad Student), Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Exam Schedule, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Experimental College, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- SUNY-Faculty Senate-Miscellaneous Materials, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Faculty Student Consolation, 1970 March 24 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Freshman Attitude Survey, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Full Opportunity Program, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Annual Report, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Undergraduate Studies, Admissions, and University College Annual Report, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Annual Reports, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Report of the University College Task Force on University Scholars, First Draft, 1970 February 5 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Office of Undergraduate Studies- Policy Memoranda, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- S/U Grading Policy Surveys, Memoranda and Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- A Working Paper of Established Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Undergraduate Academic Policy, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Memorandums on Student Advancement, 1968; 1975 (Box 7, Folder 18)